<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vidya Vikas College</string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="setting_notice">setting function only available for Head Of Department, Vice Principal and Principal.</string>


    <string name="home_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
         <head></head>
         <body style="text-align:justify;color:black;">
          Vidya Vikas Education Society’s Vikas College of Arts, Science and
          Commerce affiliated to the University of Mumbai was started in 1986, located in Vikhroli,
          a central suburb of Mumbai.
            The premises covers an area of about 64,000 sq.ft, well occupied with
          classrooms, library, gymkhana, computer laboratory, office, different
          departments of Arts, Science and Commerce, canteen facility, science
          laboratories, and well developed sports grounds.
          The college has been awarded A Grade by National Assessment and Accreditation
          Council (NAAC), Bangalore, in February 2017. The college functions throughout
          the day from 7.00 am to 5.00 pm and at night from 5.00 pm to 10.00 pm
          including administrative work. Various undergraduate and
          postgraduate programmes are conducted by different departments.
         </body>
        </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="about_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
         <head></head>
         <body style="text-align:justify;color:black;">
         <p>
            It was in 1974 that after a long process of reclaiming the waste land in Kannamwar Nagar, Vikhroli,
            the foundation was laid for the present building of the institution.
            Planted in one room at Pantnagar, Ghatkopar, this tree of Knowledge has grown up with the following
            24 branches of education.
         </p>
         <p>
            With an objective of holding light to those in darkness and extending support to helpless and guide
            those who have lost direction, our kind hearted, socially concerned and dedicated reformers laid down
            the foundation of Vidya Vikas Education Society in 1962, to impart higher education to the masses,
            especially,the weaker and underprivileged sections of society. Late Dr. W.S. Matkar, Ex. MLA.,
            Maharashtra State, Late Dr. Datta Samant, Renowned Trade Unionist and Ex. MP, Union of India and
            Shri P.M. Raut, Recipient of the National Award for Teaching and present secretary of the institution
            are the founder members of the institution. The institution could reach a remarkable milestone in the
            field of education in a very short span of time. Started with an initial strength of 260students, it
            has now grown up both qualitatively and quantitatively in to 19 educational units imparting knowledge
            to more than 15,000 students from KG level to PG level.
         </p>
         <p>
            All the members of Vidya Vikas Education Society family are fortunate to be guided and supported in
            their mission of education by Shri P.M. Raut, Secretary, Vidya Vikas Education Society and Mrs. Vidya
            P.Raut, Chief Executive Officer of the institution, both being the recipient of the National Award for
            Teaching.
         </p>
         </body>
        </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="nss_text">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
         <head></head>
         <body style="text-align:justify;color:black;">
         <p>
            The <b> National Service Scheme (NSS)</b> is an Indian government-sponsored public service program <b>conducted by the Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports
            of the Government of India</b>. Popularly known as <b>NSS</b>.
         </p>
         <p>
            At Vikas College of Arts, Science and Commerce NSS started in 2000
         </p>
         </body>
         </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="library_text">
        <![CDATA[
             <html>
         <head></head>
         <body style="text-align:justify;color:black;">
         <p>
          Books have always been a source of inspiration to many and so do
          the libraries that equip them. Libraries play a very important role
          in the development of the society. There is a give and take
          relationship between the libraries and the society. What it gives to
          the society gets back manifold and this process continues hence a
          library is said to be a growing as well as a developing organism.
          In this information age, libraries have a challenging role to play.
          Thus It has been upgraded from a traditional library to an automated
          library, further to electronic and now to digital library.
          This changing role of library has been very well acknowledged by
          the library of Ramniranjan Jhunjhunwala College. We have an excellent
          library. It has a treasure trove of information and over a decade
          now the library has come a long way in terms of its resources as
          well as the services that it provides to its user.
        </p>
        <p>
          Books play a very important role in everyone’s life, especially
          in a students’ life. They are our best friends because they inspire
          us to do great things in life and overcome our failures. We learn a
          lot of things from them. Books are our best companions as they
          provide us knowledge unconditionally without asking anything in return.
        </p>
        <p>
          Friendship with good books makes you a good person. In case when
          there is no one for your help, only these will become your
          companion in life. Books will always be there for you in your
          adverse times and bring positive value to our life.
        </p>
        </body>
         </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="library_book_detail">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
         <head></head>
         <body style="text-align:justify;color:black;">
         <h3>LIBRARY COLLECTIONS</h3>
        <table class="table">
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Total Number of Books</td>
              <td>45019</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Book Bank</td>
              <td>16434</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Journals & Periodicals</td>
              <td>37</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Bounded Book of Periodicals</td>
              <td>281</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>CD/VCD/DVD</td>
              <td>158</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>PohotoFrames of India Laureater</td>
              <td>135</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Book for Competitive Examination</td>
              <td>1300</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Sitting Capability of the Library(Student)</td>
              <td>135</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Sitting Capability of the Library(Teacher)</td>
              <td>10</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
         </body>
         </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="telephone1">(022) - 25783540</string>
    <string name="telephone2">(022) - 25784267</string>
    <string name="email">info@vikascollege.org</string>
    <string name="website">http://www.vikascollege.org</string>
    <string name="address"> Kannamwar Nagar - 2, Vikhroli (East),
            Mumbai - 400 083,  Maharashtra, India.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>